So they've got us building a messaging app,
think iMessage, WhatsApp,
whatever one you want to think of.
You would think with so many of them
that this would be easy to do.
It is most definitely not easy to do.
Game plan, a lot of planning,
a lot of working with the, with cursor
and just trying to figure out what to do next for things.
It's going not great.
Well, well, it's going all right.
It's just, it's really making me stressed out a little
with so many bugs and things to deal with.
When testing with the Android emulators,
since I don't have an Android physical device,
so that's most of the challenge I feel like.
What have I learned?
I've learned once again, why I don't want to do mobile dev,
why I never wanted to get into this.
I don't even really want to touch my own phone anymore.
This is hurting me.